So I just want to tap in and let y'all know something.
Operate my shop like a Caribbean restaurant.
You're going to get high quality and attitude.
Okay?
If I feel even a semblance of snark in a customer service email,
I will just refund you.
Okay?
I want you to understand this.
Because this is not my purpose in life.
It supports my purpose in life.
So when you support, you're going to get your goods.
However, if I feel even a dash, a sprinkle of snark,
I'm going to refund you your money.
Like somebody this morning sent me an email that was almost cool.
And then that little person inside of them,
that little audacity inside of them popped out.
No, you can't snark back.
No, I'm snarky to the general public.
You don't get to be snarky with me.
No.
So, you know, they said, you know,
I got a shipping notice, but I never received my item.
Cool.
I'll look into it.
But before I could even do that,
they then added, I mean, over 30 days.
That seems like a long time for, hold on.
I'm going to tell you.
I'm going to tell you exactly what was said so I can make sure that I nail it.
That seems, look at this person.
They placed their order.
Okay, now that I will look into.
Because I don't know why they haven't gotten their order yet.
But this person said,
Ordered this in early October.
Pretty long turnaround time.
What's the holdup?
Question mark.
Please let me know where my order is.
You don't even got to worry.
Because now you don't got an order to worry about.
That's it.
What's the holdup?
What are you talking to?
So, when you guys are communicating with small businesses this holiday season,
just remember, just remember that nine times out of ten,
you're talking to the person who's actually doing the job.
And someone said, sounds like a valid question.
And that's why your ass would get refunded too.
Because if you think saying to someone,
what's the holdup, is a valid way to approach them,
then you were not raised correctly.
What do you mean, what if the order was already on the way?
I ship the orders.
What part of that do you not seem to understand?
I say this over and over and over to y'all.
I ship the orders.
No.
Y'all love to give everybody grace.
I don't got it.
I'm giving grace to everybody.
I don't got grace to hand out to random people on the internet.
Y'all love it though.
What if they're autistic and they don't know how to communicate?
So, hello, I'm curious why this package still has not been shipped when I received the email.
That's not, like stop it.
And it's always white people.
It's always white people talking about giving grace.
Always.
Because y'all want all the grace.
Y'all want all the grace.
Y'all want grace for not knowing that you was racist.
You want grace for not realizing the United States is racist.
Y'all want grace for accidentally saying racist shit.
That's really what it is.
Y'all love to talk about grace.
Grace this, grace that.
I don't got a lot of grace for nonsense.
And everything is not required to me the same level of grace.
I'm not sending you medication.
I'm sending you a pin.
Clinton, go look on my page.
How many times have I talked about this?
I'm sending you a pin.
So y'all, that's it pretty girl J.
That's it.
And trust me, many people email me and it is completely normal and respectful.
The person before them said,
Hi Miss Amanda Seals.
I know you are super busy with the tour and packing and shipping right now.
I haven't gotten my land to land bubble.
I thought maybe you could send it along with the Malcolm bundle at one time.
Ba-dum-bum.
There you go.
And I don't even know why they didn't get their bundle.
So now I got to look into that.
But this whole like, you know, we got to, you got to send everything off.
Like it's just too much.
And I am, I am Chano's.
You ain't Jesus.
Ask Jesus for grace, not Amanda.
So again, understand, I am a Caribbean woman.
This little shop here, amandalanexparts.com, this operates like a Caribbean restaurant.
You're going to get high quality.
You're going to get high quality and high attitude.
So that is what you can expect.
High quality and high attitude.
So I really don't want to deal with all of the extraness.
I don't want it.
And again, if I feel any kind of discomfort, I'm just refunding you.
I'm just refunding you.
Because I don't even want you working around with my work on your body.
So now all you understand, what to expect.
Okay?
So all you could come and, you know, you could order my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say?
You can get a Malcolm X pin and a bundle.
As you can see here, I am about to begin packaging the Malcolm X posters.
These are all designed by yours truly.
You can get the smart, funny and black pin.
You can get all kind of pin.
We have fascists are not your friend pin.
We have Harriet Tubman with the gun pin.
We have all kind of thing in medical shop here.
We?
The only thing that is, we do ship overseas, but I find that the rate is too high.
So we're working on a walk around for that.
But you can also, but the book, the book, the ship overseas at a normal rate.
So you can order the book to ship overseas.
So all of these things and more are available at AmandaLandExports.com.
AmandaLandExports.com.
So you could come and you could, no, not pens, pins, pins, pins, pins, like a procure, pins, pins.
I don't understand the question.
Are these prints or originals?
So you think I've painted, you think I painted a hundred of these individuals?
What are you asking?
No, it's a print.
It's a print of an original drawing.
What kind of question is that?
I'm a merchant in Korea, in the Joshua era.
That is not making no sense.
It's a print.
You give them one image and they just push it out multiple times.
Why would I do that?
So all you just understand, that when you're supporting from the AmandaLandExports shop,
you're supporting the work that I'm doing in the world.
Because they just try to hold you down.
They just try to keep you back.
You don't know who this is a print of?
You don't know who this is?
Eh eh.
How you don't know who this is?
But I find that it's very concerning.
Thank you, yes, not totally.
That is Malcolm X.
His mother and my mother are both from Grenada.
So if you're trying to purchase something to support,
that is what you're purchasing.
You're purchasing items to support somebody who is out in the world.
Shout out to Brazil.
Someone want me to shout out Brazil.
I don't know why, but I've been to Brazil and they could get a shout out.
Shout out to Brazil.
So this is what going on.
It's not that I'm sick of them or nor.
It's just that I find people that act like they don't have no sense.
They just act as if they don't have no sense.
And they just act as if they don't understand what's going on.
They just watch me around the world.
They just watch me all over the city and the tongue and the nation on book tour.
And then ask for where my book?
Where my book?
Where the book come in, so?
The book comes out on November 8th.
But you're asking where the book on November 9th.
I'll get the book to you on November 9th if the book reach out on November 8th.
No, Nick Ryan, you can't.
You could order, you could order, the book, no more signed books available for now.
I may do another thing where I'm signing the books again.
But for now, we're not signing booksy.
We're not signing book right now.
Because I have to finish and sign up all the people that order the book.
And I'm very appreciative.
I'm very appreciative of the people who order the signed book.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I am not taking for granted that people are supporting the work.
I'm not taking that for granted at all.
But, Bronxville Hotel, you understand?
They wanted the book shit before you printed the last word on the page.
I find it damn rude, we?
I'm not from Canada.
Why I know about Bill & Show in Canada?
I don't know nothing about Canada, they.
I don't know about comedy in Canada.
I don't know about business in Canada.
I really honestly, I don't know much about Canada.
I know Canada, you know, they're very racist.
And they does not treat the native Canadians they're really supposed to.
And so, yeah, that is it.
That is all I really know about Canada.
I know they say that Toronto is looking bad, bad lately.
They say Toronto is not looking good again.
They say it's really getting hard, hard, hard to live in Toronto.
So, because I find a lot of all you, you're really not, um, you're really not understanding who you're dealing with.
You know, yeah, I find it distinct that you're just dealing with a person who have a factory, I have workers, line up, just ready to just, oh, Mary from Portland, Oregon.
One, one shitting, no, let me rush and send it out.
And that is not a realistic expectation.
That is a real foolish expectation to have with me, we.
Because I am not in that situation.
You see me sit up here?
You see all the draw?
The draw fill with thing.
It's not just for, it's not just for me pretty.
What is Art Cafe?
Art Cafe where?
In Nayak?
That Israel place?
Why want my thing selling there?
Why want my thing selling some Israel shop?
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, I don't need that.
I don't need that.
Nah, I don't patronize them at all.
I finish with them.
I used to go in there and then I find out, I say, wait, I say, who owned the shop?
They tell me who owned the shop?
I say, I finish with that.
I'm not going in there again.
So that is the conversation I wanted to have with you.
Because I find that there's just a lot of misunderstanding about who you're actually working with.
And you have to have a little more, since y'all, you love to talk about grace.
Oh, God, I never see people could love grace as people on this internet.
Grace, grace, grace.
Grace on the fire.
Will and grace.
And she is Zionist too.
All you just come in, you just want all the grace.
Grace, grace.
We need grace.
And it's for no reason.
You know?
It's for no reason.
I know, I see them there.
I see them there asking for different accents and things.
That is not what's going on right now.
I am not here to do accents and things.
I am here to tell you.
This is my little shop.
Amanda Land Exports.
All right?
And when you're supporting, you're not just supporting because, oh, you're like a thing that's selling in the shop.
If that is what you're doing, then go somewhere else, please, and support that.
Okay?
Supporting me, me, you're supporting doing the work of the colonization.
That is what I am doing here.
And that is what you're supporting.
So, in doing so, please understand that I am not on the schedule of the capitalization and the oppressor and all of that.
All you're just be so busy.
Oh, uh, oh, um, Christmas and New Year and this and that.
Don't order for me and then ask me where you're coming in the time for Christmas because I don't care.
I don't care about no Christmas.
I don't care about it coming for the third night of Kwanzaa or the fourth night of Hanukkah.
I don't care about, I don't care about none of that.
But, if you order it, it's coming in 30 business days or less.
That is it.
Period.
You have a good Sunday and enjoy the rest of your Sunday hunting.
And, um, now you understand what to expect when you're coming to my little shop, AmandaLand Exports.
You're dealing with a Caribbean woman.
And, um, the fact of the matter is you're getting high quality work and high quality attitude.
High quality work and high quality attitude.
And this, Anthony Washington, you are getting blocked because you have low quality class.
Low quality class.
I'm going to start responding to y'all as if I am an old West Indian woman.
That is really where we'll start happening soon.
Because I feel as though, you know, when y'all just go to these, um, these restaurants where they're rude to you and you like it.
Oh, I like them to be rude.
Ah, it's funny.
We're going to do that.
And then maybe, maybe you understand.
Oh, yeah.
Have a good rest of your Sunday.
Yes.
Praise Jesus.